<<<<<<< HEAD
{"finalExam":[],"comments":[{"date":"2023-03-30","replies":[],"author":"9efc9cad-e516-4b30-a059-92689076c6d1","comment":"test","id":"6bb9a3fb-f42f-442c-8665-4fc4ac21b3d7"},{"date":"2023-03-30","replies":[],"author":"9cf75b11-3884-4f65-8cfd-1253f23e3a0c","comment":"These are throwing me for a loop... hehehe","id":"1e48083b-7723-48f2-8a62-cfe40311ebf6"},{"date":"2023-03-30","replies":[],"author":"9cf75b11-3884-4f65-8cfd-1253f23e3a0c","comment":"Umm what are while lloops for?","id":"f6d04cab-97b1-4567-9e8f-642d8bb9447d"},{"date":"2023-03-30","replies":[],"author":"9cf75b11-3884-4f65-8cfd-1253f23e3a0c","comment":"For loops are so useful :)","id":"5720a081-f286-4b87-b4a2-2092284ab71e"}],"reviews":[],"chapters":[{"test":[],"name":"Introduction to Python","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":""}]},{"test":[],"name":"Control Flow","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":""}]},{"test":[{"question":"Which of the following is the proper way to define a while loop?","answers":["While running:","while :running:","while running","while running:"],"correctAnswer":3},{"question":"What would this return: \ni >= 5;\nwhile i >= 2:\nprint(i)\ni = i+1?","answers":["5, 4, 3, 2, 1","4, 3, 2, 1","5, 2, 1","5, 4, 3, 2"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"Which of the following is the proper way to define a for loop?","answers":["for i in range(1, 5){ }","for i in range(1, 5):","for i in range 1, 5:","for i in range 1, 5{ }"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"How does a while loop work?","answers":["A while loop runs a certain number of times","A while loop runs until i is a certain value","A while loop runs while a condition is true","A while loop doesn't do anything"],"correctAnswer":2}],"name":"Loops","sections":[{"quiz":[],"name":"The For Loop","text":"In Python, you can use something called a loop to perform an action more than once. For example, the for loop, represented below, can allow you to perform an action a certain number of times.\n\nfor i in range(10):\n    print(i)"},{"quiz":[],"name":"The While Loop","text":"A while loop is a control flow statement in Python that allows the programmer to perform a set of instructions while a certain condition is true."}]},{"test":[],"name":"Functions","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":""}]},{"test":[],"name":"Recursive Functions","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":""}]},{"test":[],"name":"Algorithmic Design","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":""}]},{"test":[],"name":"Object-Oriented Programming","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":null}]},{"test":[],"name":"Advanced Python","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":null}]},{"test":[],"name":"NumPy and Pandas","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":null}]},{"test":[],"name":"Finishing Up","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":null}]}],"author":"8e76a50c-d843-455b-b778-7543e96e6d10","name":"python","description":"With this class you will learn Python quicker than ever before!","language":"Python","id":"37fd8b96-a0a5-491b-91cf-4dcf08f07c00","title":"Learn Python in One Month"}
=======
{"finalExam":[],"comments":[{"date":"2023-03-30","replies":[],"author":"9efc9cad-e516-4b30-a059-92689076c6d1","comment":"test","id":"6bb9a3fb-f42f-442c-8665-4fc4ac21b3d7"},{"date":"2023-03-30","replies":[],"author":"9cf75b11-3884-4f65-8cfd-1253f23e3a0c","comment":"These are throwing me for a loop... hehehe","id":"1e48083b-7723-48f2-8a62-cfe40311ebf6"},{"date":"2023-03-30","replies":[],"author":"9cf75b11-3884-4f65-8cfd-1253f23e3a0c","comment":"Umm what are while lloops for?","id":"f6d04cab-97b1-4567-9e8f-642d8bb9447d"},{"date":"2023-03-30","replies":[],"author":"9cf75b11-3884-4f65-8cfd-1253f23e3a0c","comment":"For loops are so useful :)","id":"5720a081-f286-4b87-b4a2-2092284ab71e"}],"reviews":[],"chapters":[{"test":[],"name":"Introduction to Python","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":""}]},{"test":[],"name":"Control Flow","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":""}]},{"test":[{"question":"Which of the following is the proper way to define a while loop?","answers":["While running:","while :running:","while running","while running:"],"correctAnswer":3},{"question":"What would this return: \ni = 5\nwhile i == 5:\n    print(i)","answers":["5, 4, 3, 2, 1","4, 3, 2, 1","5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5...","5, 5, 5, 5, 5"],"correctAnswer":2},{"question":"Which of the following is the proper way to define a for loop?","answers":["for i in range(1, 5){ }","for i in range(1, 5):","for i in range 1, 5:","for i in range 1, 5{ }"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"What would this return: \nfor x in range(5):\n   print(x)","answers":["0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5","1, 2, 3, 4, 5","0, 1, 2, 3, 4","1, 2, 3, 4"],"correctAnswer":2}],"name":"Loops","sections":[{"quiz":[],"name":"The For Loop","text":"In Python, you can use something called a loop to perform an action more than once. For example, the for loop, represented below, can allow you to perform an action a certain number of times.\n\nfor i in range(10):\n    print(i)"},{"quiz":[],"name":"The While Loop","text":"In Python, you can use something called a loop to perform an action more than once. For example, the for loop, represented below, can allow you to perform an action a certain number of times.\n\nfor i in range(10):\n    print(i)"}]},{"test":[],"name":"Functions","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":""}]},{"test":[],"name":"Recursive Functions","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":""}]},{"test":[],"name":"Algorithmic Design","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":""}]},{"test":[],"name":"Object-Oriented Programming","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":null}]},{"test":[],"name":"Advanced Python","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":null}]},{"test":[],"name":"NumPy and Pandas","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":null}]},{"test":[],"name":"Finishing Up","sections":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Pick blue.","answers":["Blue","Green","Pink","Purple"],"correctAnswer":0}],"name":"Section 1","text":null}]}],"author":"8e76a50c-d843-455b-b778-7543e96e6d10","name":"python","description":"With this class you will learn Python quicker than ever before!","language":"Python","id":"37fd8b96-a0a5-491b-91cf-4dcf08f07c00","title":"Learn Python in One Month"}
>>>>>>> dc7e4ef7c56ae3adb5bb08b5221ba3b1b95c079c
